Now, you're going to gradually, gently, make contact by placing
さて、今から、ゆっくりと、穏やかに、接触を取っていきます。
your thumbs somewhat in the orientation of the ventricles.
親指を脳室の向きに少し合わせて。
With a light hand, good contact with your elbows and
軽い手で、肘との良好な接触を保ち、
good contact with your...
そしてあなたの...との良好な接触を。
May your whole body, your whole mind, be at
あなたの全身、あなたの精神の全てが、
your service.
奉仕するように。
for your patient.
患者さんのために。
The thumbs must be light.
親指は軽くあるべきです。
The hand must be homogeneous, if possible.
可能であれば、均一な手が必要です。
You don't feel too much pressure at the top or bottom.
上部や下部に過剰な圧力がかかっていると感じられないように。
Open your hands wide, wide, wide.
さあ、手を大きく、大きく、大きく開いてください。
And first,
そしてまず、
try to have a vision of the space.
空間の視点を持つように努めてください。
around you, around your past.
あなたの周り、そして患者さんの周り（の空間）を。
You always work with
あなたは常に、
this field
この場（フィールド）と
around the past.
患者さんの周りの（場）で働きます。
Even if you go inside,
たとえ内部に入っていくとしても、
you must be spacious in your mind,
あなたの精神は広々としているべきです、
spacious in the system.
システムにおいても広々としているべきです。
Even if you
たとえあなたが
enter the tissue,
組織の中に入っていくとしても、
you always give
あなたは常に与えます
this notion of space.
この空間の概念を。
It always needs space.
常に空間が必要です。
The embryonic force needs space to express itself.
胚性力は、発現するために空間を必要とします。
It needs growth and space.
それは成長と空間を必要とします。
And now you put yourself in the presence of your hands and you feel like
そして今、あなたは自分の手の存在を感じ、まるで
a thread that
一本の糸が
rises from your hands.
あなたの手から昇っていくのを感じます。
Towards your brain, you feel, there,
脳に向かって、感じる、ほら、
as it all opens up, you feel a connection from your hands
このように全てがうまく開くように、あなたの手から繋がりを感じる
to your brain, you let
あなたの脳へ、委ねる
your brain there, the power of your brain, you trust
そこにあるあなたの脳、あなたの脳の力に、信頼する
your receptors, you trust your hands.
あなたの受容器に、あなたの手に信頼を置く。
You try to perceive well, to distinguish the
よく知覚し、区別しようと試みる
first layer, which is the hair, or not.
最初の層である髪の毛を、あるいはそうでないものを。
It's about feeling these hairs with your fingers.
あなたの指でこれらの髪の毛を感じることです。
You make a map in your head.
あなたの頭の中でマッピングを行います。
There, that's the frequency of the hair, that's easy.
ほら、これが髪の毛の周波数、これは簡単です。
It's the visible layer, you see.
それは目に見える層です、わかるでしょう。
And then, little by little,
そして、少しずつ、
you feel that his hair is attached to the skin.
その髪の毛が皮膚に付着しているのを感じます。
You put yourself more on the skin.
より皮膚に意識を向けます。
You try
試みる
not to move.
動かないように。
You try not to move.
動かないように試みます。
in your perception, just in the feeling.
あなたの知覚の中で、ただ感覚の中で。
And there, you already feel the difference between this first layer and the skin.
そして今、この最初の層と皮膚との間の違いをすでに感じています。
And there, you will gradually enter,
そして今、あなたは少しずつ入っていきます、
with your field, you enter very gently,
あなたのフィールドで、そっと浸透させながら、
to now feel the bone structure,
今度は骨構造を感じるために、
the outer bone,
外骨を、
the hair, the skin
髪の毛、皮膚、
which is itself attached to the bone,
それ自体が骨に付着している、
which wraps the bone.
骨を包んでいるものを。
You put yourself on the bone.
骨に意識を向けます。
He tries to feel the difference.
違いを感じようと試みます。
on the outer cortex.
外皮質に。
Then with a little time, you concentrate,
そして少し時間をかけて、集中します、
you feel that you can go a little further.
さらに深く入っていくことができると感じられます。
Another density will appear, another...
別の密度が現れるでしょう、別の...
You go inside, you sift through it all.
内部に入っていき、すべてを詳細に感じ取ります。
to feel what's happening behind the bone.
骨の裏側で何が起こっているかを感じるために。
There you reach something more
そこで、あなたはより何かへと到達します。
fluidic.
流動的なものへと。
You've gone from hair to skin, to
あなたは毛髪から皮膚へ、そして
bone,
骨へと通過しました。
inner part, then you go inside.
内部の部位、そして内部へと進みます。
There you still have...
そこにはまだ...
It's still a layer that is somewhat what we call the parietal layer
それはまだ、私たちが壁側層と呼ぶところの層です。
of the dura mater.
硬膜の壁側層です。
You use the warmth of your hands to inform
あなたは手の熱を利用して伝えます。
your receptors.
あなたの受容器に。
The liquid side, up there, the
上の方にある液状の部分、
extra-encephalic compartment.
細胞外区画、
encephalic.
脳内の。
You descend further in your perception.
あなたは知覚においてさらに下降します。
to reach the very thin membranes.
非常に薄い膜に到達するために。
Perfect that we should go.
完璧に進むことができます。
This layer is mainly the most superficial layer.
この層は、特に最も表層の層です。
There, you enter very gently, very gently into the...
そこで、あなたは非常にゆっくりと、非常にゆっくりと...の中へ入っていきます。
The brain emits electricity, it's
脳は電気を発しており、それは
an interface that you feel.
あなたが感じたインターフェースです。
It's another frequency, it's a bit more electric,
それは別の周波数であり、少しより電気的で、
prickly.
ピリピリとした感覚です。
and there you descend, gently again, towards
そしてそこであなたは、さらにゆっくりと、...の方へ下降します。
the ventricular plane.
脳室レベルへ。
You cross the different layers like the gray matter,
あなたは灰白質のような様々な層を通過します。
white matter, towards the central nuclei.
白質を通り、中心核へと向かいます。
You descend, you apply yourself, you apply yourself,
深く触れ、意識を集中させ、集中させる。
You concentrate towards your thumbs to have
親指に意識を集中させ、
ventricles.
脳室を捉える。
There, you feel that the right hemisphere and the left hemisphere
そこで、右半球と左半球が
have slightly separate movements.
やや分離した動きをしているのを感じるだろう。
Thank you for watching this video!
このビデオをご覧いただきありがとうございます！
It accompanies the ventricle like a dolphin moving forward and then
それは、前進するイルカのように脳室に寄り添い、
the other hemisphere
前方へ、そして
the other with a slight delay and a delay.
半球が
It doesn't breathe at the same speed.
もう一方がわずかな遅れを伴って続く。
You play, you let yourself be guided.
それは同じリズムで動いていない。
Then when you go back layer by layer, ventricle,
そして、層ごとに戻っていくとき、脳室から、
then you go to the level of the central
次に、あなたは核のレベルへ向かう。
nuclei.
中心核のレベルへ向かう。
white matter, the cortex, the
白質、皮質、
bimed, the equitaine layer, the arachnoid,
硬膜、上衣層、蜘蛛膜、
the gemmer,
軟膜、
the inner cortex, the future tromeste,
内側皮質、将来の中胚葉、
the outer cortex, the face, the gemmer,
外側皮質、顔面、胚葉、
the sky and the skin, and then the presence at the level of the hair.
頭蓋冠、皮膚、そして毛髪のレベルでの存在。
Okay, that's good, that's good.
よし、順調だ、順調だ。
Subtitles FR?
フランス語字幕？